{
  "Programming Languages": [
    {
      "question": "Who is not a creator of a major programming language?",
      "incorrectAnswers": [
        "Bjarne Stroustrup",
        "Brendan Eich",
        "Dennis Ritchie"
      ],
      "correctAnswer": "Timo Nicolas Angst",
      "answers": [
        "Bjarne Stroustrup",
        "Brendan Eich",
        "Timo Nicolas Angst",
        "Dennis Ritchie"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which programming language is the oldest of these?",
      "answers": [
        "Python",
        "Java",
        "Go",
        "Typescript"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is not a reserved keyword in Java 16?",
      "answers": [
        "var",
        "_",
        "goto",
        "let"
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Which programming language is purely functional?",
      "answers": [
        "Javascript",
        "Haskell",
        "F#",
        "Rust"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Haskell does not have",
      "answers": [
        "First-class Functions",
        "Higher Kinded Types",
        "Dependant Types",
        "Capabilities to do IO"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Where was C created?",
      "answers": [
        "Bell Labs",
        "University of Southampton",
        "Zürich"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "CSS stands for",
      "answers": [
        "Cross Site Scripting",
        "C-Sharp Sucks",
        "Cascading Style Sheets"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Javascript is standardized as",
      "answers": [
        "ECMAScript",
        "ISOScript",
        "ANSIScript",
        "JSScript"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "The Rust programming language promises",
      "answers": [
        "Undefined Behaviour",
        "An easy learning experience",
        "Fearless Concurrency"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is WebAssembly?",
      "answers": [
        "Machine code distributed over the web",
        "Fast Javascript",
        "A compilation target language run in the browser"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which language is used for Microsoft Office Macros?",
      "answers": [
        "Coffeescript",
        "VBA",
        "Brainfuck",
        "Whitespace"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the most popular esoteric programming language?",
      "answers": [
        "Befunge",
        "Brainfuck",
        "Whitespace"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of these programming languages is multi-paradigm?",
      "answers": [
        "Javascript",
        "Idris",
        "SQL",
        "Haskell"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    }
  ],
  "AXA ITS 2020": [
    {
      "question": "Wer macht am liebsten Pausen?",
      "answers": [
        "Timo",
        "Kai",
        "Martin"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Wer würde (rein hypothetisch) am ehesten für Java Swing krank sein?",
      "answers": [
        "Corsin",
        "Noel",
        "Desirée"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Was ist Cyrills Spezialfähigkeit in Flappy Stift?",
      "answers": [
        "Whiskey-Cyrill",
        "Stift Entlassen",
        "Browser Crashen"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Wer kommt oft pünktlich 2 Minuten zu spät?",
      "answers": [
        "Rolf",
        "Alex",
        "Oliver",
        "Nils"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    }
  ],
  "Gaming": [
    {
      "question": "How is killing the entire enemy team at the same time called in Overwatch?",
      "answers": [
        "Ace",
        "Joker",
        "Team Kill",
        "Total Destruction"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    }
  ]
}